Guide to the Helen Bullard papers, 1920-1950.
Bullard, Helen papers
- Series V. Travel, 1924-1952, 1915-1954
  - Travel to Virginia, travel information and maps, and postcards. Guidebooks to Garden Week, 1947 and 1948. Brochures for historic homes on James River, Williamsburg, Monticello, and Mt. Vernon., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Travel to the Smokie Mountains via the Blue Ridge Parkway. Guidebooks, maps, brochures, ticket stubs, postcards, photograph, 2 large format color postcards., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Series VI. Oversize blueprints and drawings, 1922-1963, 1915-1954
  - Willard Clapp Project, done in the office of Warren Manning (correspondence in folder in Box 3 Folder 20): 9 blueprints (2 folded) and 2 pencil drawings on white paper, 1923 (Folder 1)
    - Willard Clapp Project, done in the office of Warren Manning (correspondence in folder in Box 3 Folder 20): 9 blueprints (2 folded) and 2 pencil drawings on white paper, 1923 (Folder 1)
      Sketch
      Rear Drive Profile and Layout, October 1923
      Map of the Clapp Property Showing Ground Elevations, May 1923
      Plan Showing Layout of Pipe Lines for Enell Irrigation System
      Plan for Grounds
      Plan Showing Water and Drain Pip Location (Proposed), July 24, 1923
      Plan of Grounds with hand written narrative.
      Study for Water Supply and Drainage, July 24, 1924
      Profile and Layout of Service Drive, October 1923
      Key Map Showing Arrangement of Planting Sheets, July 31, 1923
      Suggestion for the Arrangement and Planting of Grounds
  - City plans for Springfield, Mass.: 4 folded maps in color; 1 small plan for Utica New York., 1923 (Folder 2)
    Land Development Plan, City of Utica, NY
    City Plan Map of Springfield, Massachusetts, 1923
    Building Zone Map, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1923
    Parks Schools Playgrounds in the City of Springfield, Massachusetts, 1923
    Circulation Map of Springfield, Massachusetts
  - John W. Kiser, Esquire Project, and Estate of Mr. and Mrs. William R. Simonds Project both in Southhampton, Long Island for Annette Hoyt Flanders office,: 4 blueprints for Kiser project, 4 blueprints for Simmonds Project (all noted as Void), 1929 (Folder 3)
    Kiser Project - Plan of Steps and Pier Showing Brick Pattern with Plan Showing Revised Brick Pattern on Posts of Pool, July 19, 1929
    Kiser Project - F.S. Detail for Pickets and Stringers- (entrance gate), June 1929
    Kiser Project - Revision of Garden Layout Plan
    Kiser Project - Revision of Garden Layout Plan (marked "void" on back)
    Simonds Project - Perennial Planting Plan
    Simonds Project - Plan for Wrought Iron Work
    Simonds Project - Proposed Drive from Garage to Barn
  - Misc. garden plans: Toparian club maps (1922): 2 blueprints; Lang Memorial (no date): 3 sheets with notes and 3 pencil drawings on trace paper; Storrs Garden in Newport, RI (no date): 1 small blueprint; McCormick garden, Lake Forest, Ill.: 1 blueprint (correspondence in Box 3 folder 19); CJ Herlihy garden (1949): 1 blueprint (correspondence in Box 4 folder 14), 1922, 1949, no dates (Folder 4)
  - Misc. State work: Northern State Parkway, Long Island State Park Commission ( 1941): 2 blueprints; State Teachers College, Oneonta, New York (1944): 1 large blueprint; State Teachers College, Potsdam, New York (1953): 1 large format blueprint; State Office Building Campus, New York (1963): 1blueprint, 1941-1963 (Folder 5)
    State Office Building Campus, March 27, 1963
    Northern State Parkway - Grade Separation at South Oyster Bay Road, 4-18-41
    Northern State Parkway - Grade Separation at Burrill's Road, 4-25-41
    State Teacher's College, Potsdam, NY - Construction: Improvement of Grounds - Buildings No. 10, 12, and 13 - Detail for Walk Paving, Flagpole, and Football Goalposts, May 3, 1953
    State Teacher's College, Oneonta, NY - Preliminary Drawing - Development Plan, 11-1-44
    Herman M. Biggs Memorial Hospital, NY - Preliminary Drawing - Proposed Revisions in Landscape Development - Superintendent's Residence Building S, November 4, 1944.
  - Kiser Project, Southhampton, Long Island for Annette Hoyt Flanders office: 9 blueprints (note smaller blueprints in drawer folder 3), 1929 (Folder 6)
    Westchester County Park Commission - Playland Rye Beach Planting Plan, September 7, 1927. Revised November 17, 1927.
    Westchester County Park System - Tibbetts Brook Park - Plan of Development, Bronxville, NY, October 1924.
    Southern State Parkway Planting Plans and Lists - The Planting Plan- Old Mill Road to Station 693, September 22, 1930 (labelled "drawn by RAD").
    Southern State Parkway Planting Plans - Planting Plan for Corona and Franklin Avenue Bridges Portion W of CL Franklin Avenue.
    Estate of John W. Kiser, Southampton, L.I. - Detail Drawing of the Main Entrance, May 16, 1929 (marked VOID).